AYUSH PRATAP SINGH

+91 9792757429 webdeveloper.ayush@gmail. com Antriksh Golf View Sector 78 Noida India 06/Oct/1997

Summary

I am a Frontend Developer, BCA graduate. I have been working for the last 1.5Years in the Web Development industry primarily Web Front-end & Web Apps Development. I am working as a front-end developer for the last 1.5years. I am extremely passionate about my work. In my professional career, have done 25+ projects. I have a strong grip on the latest front-end development technologies like Html5, Css3, Sass, Bootstrap, JavaScript, and React js.

Education

Delhi Public School

2016 - 2017

Higher Secondary School

Asian Business School

2018 - 2021

BCA(Bachelor Of Computer Application)

Experience

Steer For Change Foundations

Sep 2020 - April 2021

Frontend wordpress developer

I was working as Frontend wordpress developer all the sections and pages are developed by me.

Website - sfcfoundations.com

UI Cardio

Feb 2019 - May 2019

Frontend Developer Intern

I was working as Frontend Developer. My main purpose of this internship was to learn languages and to develop problem solving skill under the supervision of my seniors.

Live Projects

Portfolio Website

2021 - Till now

I have created my own portfolio website. It got all my small projects linked inside and my resume attached if you wish to download it will directly downloaded from there. With all my contact information.

Link - www.ayushchauhan.co.in

Weather App

Jan 2022 - Till Date

This web app gives you real time weather updates of any city in the world. Just type the name and see.

 $Link\ -\ https://comfy-palmier-fce 625.net lify.app$

Skills

Frontend Development, Landing Pages, Java Script, React. js, Bootstrap, Css, Version Control Git, Responsive for all devices

Languages

English, Hindi

Interest

Wordpress Developer & Manager

Others

Name - Introduction to Programming Using Python Url https://www.guvi.in/verify certificate?id=601c6z02K1L99kP 261

Name - IAB Digital Marketing and Media Foundations Certification Url https://learndigital.withgoogle.c om/digitalunlocked/validatecertificate code

Other Projects

Split Equally, Password
Generator,
Currency Exchange, To do List,
Coffee Store
Many more are mentioned on
my website.

Social Profile

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/ayush chauhan0610/

Facebook:

facebook.com/profile.php?id=10 002 3532903004

Twitter:

twitter.com/mr_ayushchauhan







Certificate of Appreciation

presented to



for his contribution as a Front End Website Developer from 01/09/2020-31/03/2021 for Steer For Change Foundations. Your participation is highly appreciated!

Ekanali Singh

EKAWALI SINGH

Founder & Director





UlCardio - Tel : +91 720 626 4120 #1833, Sector 45, Gurgaon https://uicard.io



Date: Apr 30, 2019

Experience Letter

This letter is to certify that **Mr. Ayush Chauhan** has successfully completed his internship program of ~three months with **UlCardio**. His internship tenure was from **1st Feb 2019** to **30th Apr 2019**. He was working with the **Technology Department** and was actively & diligently involved in the projects and tasks assigned to him.

During the span, we found him punctual and hardworking person. His learning powers are good and he picks up swiftly. His feedback and evaluation proved that he learned keenly. Moreover, his interpersonal and communication skills are brilliant.

During his association with us, we have found him sincere and diligent. We wish him all success.

For further details kindly contact

Regards,

Arvind Singh (CEO and Founder)

This is an electronically generated document, hence will not be printed on letterhead material